so how do you get a th000 people on your
email list in 30 days whenever we
promote our business we always get
hundreds to thousands of people every
single month that come onto our email
list and that's exactly how we grow our
coaching business for those of you I
haven't met yet my name is Jeremiah
Kowski and I've been in the online
coaching and course space for over 21
years helping some of the top coaches
and mentors scale their businesses and
reach more clients and what I love to do
is help people whether they're just
starting out or they're already SU
successful be able to create the kind of
money that they want to make one of the
main tools that we use to do this is
marketing advertising and sales and the
big process that we to teach everybody
is how to find the right people how to
promote your business correctly to them
and then how to close more sales and
everything that you're going to find on
this channel is based around that we
just released a brand new Facebook ads
class it's free you'll find it below in
the links in the description you can go
check that out I think it'll really help
if you want to know how to use Facebook
ads to attract more clients and get them
to become a part of your business now
when it comes to getting people on your
email list the number one reason why
somebody's going to join your email list
is because there's some kind of a thing
that they're going to get for doing so
there's some kind of value exchange
that's going to happen when they join
your email list people are not just
going to join your email list nobody
wants to get more emails like understand
that right nobody wants to get more
emails so why would people join your
email list and then you might be saying
well yeah then I don't want them to join
my email is because nobody wants to get
more emails listen I want you to
understand this email is not dead people
are buying through email and the number
one way to grow your coaching or course
business is to grow your email list so
you got to have something of value that
you are giving people in exchange for
their email address here's one of the
mistakes I see a lot of coaches and
mentors make and I don't want you to
make it which is why I'm mentioning this
right now is that a lot of times they
give value away and it's really good
value it's tremendous it's exceptional
it's amazing but the problem is that
they're not asking for anything in
exchange now that's awesome and I
understand again the law of reaping and
sewing I understand give and it shall be
given unto you but when it comes to
business you got to put on your
marketing hat if you want to be
successful I meet so many exceptional
mentors coaches and course creators with
some of the best content and they don't
ask for an email address they don't ask
for a phone number they don't ask for a
connection and what are their sales zero
and then they come to me saying Jeremiah
I'm doing all the right things but
nobody's buying from me nobody's
becoming a client of mine in my own
business I struggled with this because I
thought that that was exactly how to do
things that I wanted to honor people's
autonomy and agency to be able to decide
if they want to work with me without
ever actually asking for an opportunity
to do so can I tell you this you're
you're only going to get what you ask
for and when you're honest with people
about what you want you'll get it again
I would love to help you grow your
business and that's exactly why we have
trainings like the free training on
Facebook ads that's in the description
like my accelerator program where I work
with people every single week to build
out their offers their landing pages
their advertising campaigns to be able
to scale their businesses but if I don't
tell people about what I have to offer
and by the way for years I didn't
because I was afraid that people
wouldn't they didn't want to be sold and
I didn't want to be salesy and I didn't
want to seem like all I cared about was
money all of these things we got to lay
those aside again when your purpose is
helping another person you owe it to
them to be able to tell them about what
you have to offer now one of the
questions people ask me is this is
Jeremiah okay I get that but how do I
not give away too much value okay
twofold here
first off we want to address what we
call scarcity thinking operate out of an
abundance mindset and by the way an
abundance mindset has nothing to do with
how much money you have what your
position is or what you're currently
doing or operating in you can have an
abundance mindset when your bank account
is negative when you're in the red when
you have insufficient funds coming in
and I can tell you this is that in the
times in my life when our business
struggled years ago that the only way
that I was able to pull us out of that
was to be able to see myself as somebody
that had tremendous value and that had
Authority in the space that I was
operating in now you might say well
Jeremiah or somebody with insufficient
funds they got no Authority in that
space can I tell you
this sometimes where you're at today is
not where you're going forever and it's
not where you've always been and I want
you to remember the great things that
you've done in your life the exceptional
value that you've delivered to people
the things that you know and the
knowledge that helps other people and
then when you can take what solves a
problem for somebody and you're able to
give that to them that's why I give away
trainings like how to do Facebook ads
like the the one below or like in this
video the reason why I make these videos
is out of an abundance mindset to be
able to share what I know with people
before they even spend any money with me
and so the the key to be able to
actually grow your email list is
identifying what do people actually want
that you can give them here's one of the
problems a lot of people want to give
what people need and that's the issue
you have to base what you're giving off
of what somebody
desires off of what they truly truly
want again I would love to give my wife
a Corvette for
Christmas she might think it's cool but
honestly that's what I want
okay but when my wife comes to me and
says hey you know what I would love this
amazing new bed frame
set quite frankly I don't really care
about how the bed frame set is but
listen if she likes it happy wife you
know the rest and in that I'm able to
give what she wants and desires we know
that in friendship in marriage that
there's a give and take there and it's
the same thing when it comes to your
business we think of
so logically about things and that's one
of the mistakes that we make is that we
know that it's it's just business people
say right but here's the thing people
become your clients on emotion on how
you make them feel on how they feel
about the
interaction and there's a process that
occurs before they become your client
right we're so focused on the dollar
signs that we miss
the
process which goes like
this we have free content that we give
to people right that could be in the
form of videos like this that could be
in the form of free classes that could
be in the form of a free ebook from
there people give us something they give
us their email address okay so they give
us their email address and what I'm
doing is this is based on cost okay
email address that's all we want we're
bribing them with some kind of value for
the email address now here's the thing
even if somebody does not consume the
thing that I give them I'm okay with
that and here's why because I'm going to
continue to email them so that they give
me the next level which is their
time and if I can get somebody to give
me their time meaning that they are
connected with me for every hour that I
spend with somebody what do I mean spend
with somebody I don't mean that I'm
sitting down actively with people I mean
every hour that people sit down and
watch content with me people are willing
to spend at least
$1,000 with me in my business and that's
the case with nearly every business that
we have found in fact if you're really
really good at how you deliver your
content and being persuasive and selling
you can even increase this to two or
even $3,000 and I know mentors that have
actually been able to do that for every
hour that they spend with somebody they
can get $3 to $5,000 in exchange for
that one hour that's a skill set that's
a that that's a skill issue but for most
people that are just starting out maybe
you're just starting out in your
business right you're like I don't I I
don't have a lot of skill all you got to
do is get people to give you their email
address in exchange for value and what
this is is this is based on the free
content is based on attention Okay so
we're getting people's attention in some
way we're asking for their email address
right here so this is an
exchange of some kind this is the first
value exchange they are exchanging their
email address and they could even give
you a fake email address there's ways to
mitigate that if you make sure that they
have to actually access the email to be
able to get the content that mitigates
that and then they give you their time
there's a difference that happens
between the email value exchange and the
time exchange and here's here's how the
difference works here is that somebody
might give you their email address but
they're busy they got a life just like
you and I do and they they have a lot of
things going on in their life and so how
do they make sure that they're actually
getting the most out of that well they
ignore a lot of things that come in they
sign up for stuff and never watch it and
it's not because they're bad people it's
not because they're the wrong people
either by the way some of the right
people actually are that but when you
get somebody to give you their time
something happens because when somebody
gives you their time they are
invested you know football season about
to start I'm a I'm a I'm a fan of the
Kansas City Chiefs that's that's been my
team for for a long time and and I'm
excited because even at the time of
recording this video their first game is
tonight I hope they win I am invested
with that team because of the time that
I spent okay maybe not sports but what
about gardening or parenting the more
time that we spent or a relationship
dating or in a church or reading a book
reading a novel there's a there's a
great novel right here that I was I was
reading recently uh cord of thorn and
Roses little bit spicy but it's a it's a
good
one I was
invested into that novel by by chapter
7even and that's when it starts to
really pick up and I just I couldn't put
it down it took me a little while to get
inv it's actually took me like four
months to get invested at that level
into the book let me adjust it on my
shelf here took me a little while to get
invested into the
novel but then I couldn't put it down
because of I wanted to see what was
going to happen next it was a page
Turner and so with that when people give
you their time they are willing to buy
more and more and more from you I'm I
plan on reading the entire series I'm
about to start the second book here next
month I got a lot of other I love novels
by the way it's something I love I got a
lot of my favorite ones up here I also
have some of my favorite marketing books
some my favorite books
about creating sales and business like
irresistible offer by Mark Jord one of
the classic books of online marketing or
The Ultimate Sales letter by Dan Kennedy
by the way these are two of the greatest
mentors in the online marketing space
and one of the things that you need to
understand is that when you can create
an irresistible
offer and you're able to use sales
letters to be able to connect with
people what is a sales letter well let
me show you an example of a sales letter
so for the training that we have going
on right now this is a sales letter this
is a free class it's over at my website
get more coaching clients with Facebook
ads and AI so this is a sales letter to
get some somebody to register for this
training there's there's a title to it
there's a a
headline there's what is included what's
going to be shown there's testimonies of
clients that have been successful with
our information and a forum for people
to sign up and a little bit about me and
that's what we call a sales letter and
what a good sales letter does is it
connects with the desire that somebody
has showing the you can solve a problem
and let me read this here in this book
right here one of my favorite sections
of this book talks about the smart
Market diagnosis questions what keeps
them awake at night what is the number
one thing that keeps your prospects up
at night what are they most afraid
of gosh why do we even want to think
about that
right that's
negative it's not because you're going
to be including the negativity in your
offer when you create an offer
you want to show people that you have
the ability to move them from
Pain
to
pleasure and this is whatever they
desire the most the pain that they're in
is what you're moving them away from
this is their desire now if all we did
in our offer was lead with the pain
listen nobody would buy it I've tried it
it doesn't work it might be a great way
to get some attention of people and
listen we live in a social media world
where people are in pain people are
experiencing a lot of pain and suffering
and struggling and it's time for us to
give people a Lifeboat out of those
things it's time for us to show people
that there's a better way to do
things and so your offer shows them that
you can deliver what they desire now
maybe you might say Jeremiah I don't
believe that I can deliver what I desire
what they desire can I tell you this I
know that you can and that's exactly
what I Mentor people with in my classes
and in my trainings and in my coaching
program is how to package and create the
best irresistible offer that gets people
to buy from you and so listen if you're
somebody who's watching this right now
and you want to grow a coaching business
or an online course business or
Consulting business I would love to work
with you to help you dial in your
messaging to get your sales right to
know exactly who to reach what what's
your best Niche or topic and all of the
above inside of my accelerator program
when we open the doors there's a link to
get on the waiting list to my
accelerator program in the time being be
sure to check out some of the classes
that we have to offer and so in this
when you know how to move people from
pain over to pleasure and get them the
desires that they
want you're able to grow your email
list by doing this okay so you might say
well I don't know what those things are
well let's talk about that here real
quickly is if you are beginning and
you've not created a course or a
coaching program then we want to
identify what is a topic that you can
help people with and then you create
something related to what those people
are dealing with you know artificial
intelligence is one of the coolest tools
that we can use today to be able to
brainstorm a lot of these ideas and it's
absolutely free as well chat GPT is
right here if I just type in this I want
to
help people solve a problem that I can
charge money for in a course give me a
100 ideas look at this chat gbt can go
to work and give us a hundred ideas of
how we can help people solve a problem
in their life whether it be Financial
digital marketing technology related or
let's just stop this right here
watch what about about more life
skills things like people who would be
interested in gardening or glass blowing
or art give a 100 ideas that are
unrelated to those ideas and by the way
I misspelled some of that but chat GPT
can read between the lines you don't
need to be perfect with your spelling
the AI is really good at knowing what
we're talking about okay so you can show
people how to do uh again gardening
related things you can show them how to
do arts and crafts you can show them and
I and I want to This Is How We can
brainstorm with this go even deeper
brainstorm other niches or ideas that
are not Arts gardening or other related
okay watch this here's a deep dive into
other skills or Hobbies outdoor survival
skills um let's see health and wellness
holistic health packages so again you're
getting the idea as to what that is and
maybe you're saying J
I I okay this is all great I know what I
help people with but how do I actually
get them on my email list you haven't
told me yet how we actually get them on
our email list okay so what you do is
you figure
[Applause]
out what are those problems that they
want to solve and you create something
in the form of either a
video or an ebook or some kind of
training and really this is across the
board what we do when we create an offer
that grows our email list some kind of
training we're even getting the place
now with artificial intelligence where
you can use AI to create software you
could create software for cooking or
software for uh gardening or things like
that again I don't want to say that you
need to do that but that's an idea for
some people if they know how to do
things like that you create some kind of
value that you're going to deliver but
you're only going to give it to people
when they give you their email address
okay now how do we find those people
that are going to give us their email
address right we know that we got to
create this offer but where are they
right now well right now they're on
social media they're on Instagram
they're on YouTube they're on Tik Tok
they're on Facebook and they're all over
the place in all these different places
but here's what you don't want you don't
want to do this you don't want to worry
about well how do I pull all these
people together and build my audience
first no what you want to focus in on is
what is one topic that I could create a
training for that I can deliver to
people when they give me their email
address what is one idea that I can
create something for that they can give
me their email address for and then we
start marketing that to people we start
putting it out there on our social media
we start talking about it everywhere on
YouTube on Facebook on Instagram or just
Master One platform and then once you
get those people people onto your email
list this gives you an opportunity to
take it a step further because that
doesn't stop with the email list it goes
further just getting people on your
email list is great but that's simply
not
enough maybe it was years ago but
nowadays it isn't you have to now
nurture that connection what does
nurture look like
nurture let's actually look up the
dictionary definition of
nurture I'm really curious as to what
this word means training upbringing uh
sustaining food something that g gives
an organism
nourishment to educate to further the
development of or to Foster and I think
that's the better term furthering the
development of or fostering nowadays
when people just get on our email list
the chances of them even going through
the content are very very small because
they're being inundated with so much
messaging that's out there
but when you can then nurture that
connection with people by delivering
additional pieces of content such as in
the form of a YouTube video or the form
of another piece of content that solves
a deeper problem that they have when you
make an offer to somebody about what you
have for sale your course your coaching
program your training they will want to
buy it because now you've established
yourself as an authority in their mind
they see you as somebody that they can
trust that they want to work with and
that they want to learn from and that's
exactly why I put out videos like this
is this is part of how I nurture that
connection with people this is part of
how we deepen that connection with
people and so again if you want to grow
your email list to a thousand people
this month right now the way that we do
so effectively it starts with
identifying what is our irresistible
offer and then we start to promote that
out to people that are out there we
start to dial in
okay who do we want to reach where are
they right now we can start to Market to
those people we start talking about what
that thing is we start growing our email
list with those people on there and then
the best way to actually get a thousand
people onto your email list this month
is by using advertising a lot of times
when we do just organic or unpaid
marketing it's a trickle just a few
people maybe five people here 10 people
here but if you want to get a thousand
people on your email list in one month
going over to using something like
Facebook ads or Instagram ads which I
have that training below this video that
you can watch where I show you exactly
how to put those together that will
attract those people to you in your
offer you can get hundreds and even
thousands of people for just a few
dollars onto your email list it doesn't
cost a lot it's not a lot of effort to
do when you follow this process and so I
break down for you in that training
exactly how to do that in my accelerator
program I break down four people inside
of our program I'm working with them I
come alongside you in my coaching
program to walk you through step by step
on how to get those results listen if
you want to jump into my accelerator
program and skip the line for that head
on over to my Instagram and send me a
direct message and let me know Jeremiah
I want into your accelerator program
just tell me that and I'll get you going
on there I'll send you the document
about all the information and I'll show
you how to get started with that okay
listen I'd love to continue working with
you I'd love to talk with you I'd love
to see you in one of my classes go check
that out and learn exactly how to get
those people on your list with Facebook
ads I think you're really going to love
it and subscribe to this channel we'll
talk soon have a good one